oneweekseason.com 2019-12-21

# Privacy Policy - One Week Season

#### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is part of the Terms of Service (“Terms”) that governs your access to or use of TOWS’ Service. Each capitalized term used in this Privacy Policy has the meaning ascribed to it in the Terms, unless such term is defined in this Privacy Policy.  
  
The Privacy Policy describes how and when we collect, use, or share your information when you use the Service, and applies to all visitors, users, or others who access the Service (“users”). If you do not want TOWS to collect, store, use, or share your information in the ways described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use the Service.  
  
This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information collected by TOWS other than information collected through the Service. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to TOWS through the Service or through any other means. 

**1.** **Information Collection and Use by TOWS** **.**  
We store the information we collect on our encrypted systems or licensed systems, and use it for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. You authorize TOWS to use or store your information in, or transfer your information to, the United States and any other country where we operate. Privacy and data protection laws in some countries may vary from the laws in the country where you live. We use your information to provide and improve the Service, for identification or authentication, for targeted online or offline marketing, to contact members or interested parties, and for general research or reporting. If you provide information to TOWS for a certain reason, we may use the information in connection with the reason that it was provided.  
  
We collect the following types of information:  
  
**1.1. Information you provide to TOWS directly.** This includes the personal information you provide for your TOWS account, such as your name, username, location, password, email address, phone number, profile information, or other contact information. This also includes communications between you and TOWS. If you provide TOWS with your phone number, you agree to receive text messages to that number from TOWS. We may use your information to send you information about our Service, to market to you, to help prevent spam, fraud, or abuse, including through third-party services or applications.  
  
**1.2. Cookies and Automated Information Collection.** We may store log files or use tracking technologies such as cookies, pixels, web beacons, or local storage to collect information about how you use the Service or to provide features to you. We may also collect similar information from emails sent to you that then help TOWS track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by you. This information allows for more accurate reporting and improvement of the Service. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level.  
  
**1.3. Analytics and Third-Parties.** We may use a variety of third-party services, including analytics tools, to help provide the Service or to measure or improve the use of the Service. These third-party service providers may use tracking technologies to collect information sent by your device, and may share such information with TOWS.  
  
**2.** **Information Collection and Use by Stripe** **.**  
We partner with Stripe, Inc. (“Stripe”) to facilitate card and other payments. Stripe is responsible for the personal information it process or collects. Your agreement with Stripe will govern your relationship with Stripe.  
  
**3.** **Information Sharing and Disclosure** **.**  
We may disclose or publish your non-personal information or non-personal information about you for industry analysis, demographic profiling, marketing, analytics, or other business purposes. We may also share your information or allow third-parties to collect your information, which may include personal information, in the following circumstances:  
  
**3.1. Your Consent.** With your consent, we may share your information with third-parties or allow them to collect your information from the Service in ways not specifically described in this Privacy Policy.  
  
**3.2. Other Users.** The Service may support interaction with other users. If so, users will be able to see your activity on the Service, communicate with you within the Service, or view your profile, which may include your user name and other profile information. You may optionally choose to provide and publicly display your full name and other personal information.  
  
**3.3. Service Providers.** We may share your information with third-party organizations that help TOWS provide the Service to you. Our Service providers will be given access to your information as is reasonably necessary to provide the Service under reasonable confidentiality terms.  
  
**3.4. Change of Control.** In the event that we are involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization, or sale of assets, we may sell or transfer your information as part of the transaction. The Terms and this Privacy Policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity. We will make reasonable efforts to let you know of the change of control before transferring your personal information.  
  
**3.5. Law and Harm.** We may access, preserve, or disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to: (i) comply with a law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request; (ii) protect the safety of any person; (iii) address fraud, illegal activity, security, or technical issues; or (iv) protect our rights or property. However, nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to limit any legal defenses or objections that you may have to a third-party’s request to disclose your information.  
  
**4.** **How to Access and Modify Your Information** **.**  
If you are a registered user of the Service, we provide you with tools and account settings to access, correct, delete, or modify the personal information you provided to TOWS or associated with your account. You can request access to additional information by contacting TOWS. We may retain your information for as long as necessary for our business purposes or for legal requirements. Please note that search engines and other third-parties may still retain copies of your public information, like your user profile information, even after you have deleted the information from the Service or deactivated your account.  
  
**5.** **Withdrawing Consent** **.**  
You have the right to withdraw your consent to our processing of your information and your use of the Service. You can do this at any time by closing your account through your account settings and then emailing TOWS to request that your personal information be deleted. If you withdraw your consent to the use or sharing of your personal information for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, you may not have access to any of the Service, and we might not be able to provide you any of the Service. Please note that we may continue to process your information after you have withdrawn consent and requested that we delete your information if we have a legal basis to do so. For example, we may retain certain information if we need to do so to comply with an independent legal obligation, or if it is necessary to do so to pursue our legitimate interest in keeping the Service safe and secure.  
  
**6.** **Our Policy Concerning Children** **.**  
The Service is not for children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under 13. Children under 13 should not use the Service at any time. If we learn that we have inadvertently gathered personal information from a child under 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact TOWS.  
  
**7.** **Contact TOWS** **.**  
If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy, the Service, the Terms, or our practices, please send an e-mail to info@jmtowin.com.
